<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[My Personal Blog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just a personal Blog to document random stuff in my professional and personal life.]]></description><link>https://fidel95.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 05:17:54 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[How is my college life]]></title><description><![CDATA[Who would believe that this undocumented person from Indiana was going to get a full ride to college and would have to move to a completely…]]></description><link>https://fidel95.github.io/college-life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fidel95.github.io/college-life/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 01:01:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://desu.edu/&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot; style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; max-width: 630px; &quot;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 32.911392405063296%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&amp;apos;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABQAAAAHCAYAAAAIy204AAAACXBIWXMAAC4jAAAuIwF4pT92AAABtUlEQVQoz42Ry2sTYRTF588UcSOiIiIao6KQhPooSHRRraXdqK24qouuig/aUvuiTSYP0kwnyWSSZl6ZNCGxpqaTmWR+ftalXXjgcuCecy+Xc6WRH6Alkhzdi3N8aOIh4Pv8D8JzfNJitctLrc/yx2Xev/mEUdTovppjcFDm+PMKXqWK33TxW0f4lsPQsPAMG69cpTPzlpPvO/hOk0GucOaVEimbyd0Gd7Jtvk4tMPq2QjcxiXXxKuaFKzi3H2Fei+BE41g3ojjXI7SjMVovpnEfJ3HuxrCFxxL9P7qUTFtElZ/Mf8nQjQihZrGxtEYrlaexuk1/L8O4qBCUNbx0BmNLRk8XCcsVBnKewf4BJzspTosqv9JZJJEEtflF2rcegKqy3g24v2tzabVORPCU0uHmpsGE7PC80OZJ1uXyWp05tUNj+G+u0mzWJPZ6iQ9bpbOG1u7zdFNnQtSzbTGYs3m4rjOdsXiXt4lv1JjNmIJ1eqeBuGeMPxSbx2PC0Qhpoeiy9yNgpuDi9j3CYIgsy5T2C+jlEoZepWk0qGkVVEXBrNcwDuukCwoNwblcjl6v9/frYchvEGzjkz2S39wAAAAASUVORK5CYII=&amp;apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot; alt=&quot;dsu&quot; title=&quot;dsu&quot; src=&quot;/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/f058b/dsu.png&quot; srcset=&quot;/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/c26ae/dsu.png 158w,
/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/6bdcf/dsu.png 315w,
/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/f058b/dsu.png 630w,
/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/40601/dsu.png 945w,
/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/78612/dsu.png 1260w,
/static/de328e2cc00198603b9e44c4b7ec56b4/e332b/dsu.png 1929w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px&quot; style=&quot;width:100%;height:100%;margin:0;vertical-align:middle;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Who would believe that this undocumented person from Indiana was going to get a full ride to college and would have to move to a completely different state? Not me, that is for sure, as my friend was driving me to campus, which is located in Dover, Delaware, which is also an 11-hour drive. I was thinking to myself what is awaiting me, unsure of that answer, I closed my eyes and woke up right before arriving on campus. It finally hit me I am a college student now; unfortunately, my first semester of college was happening while we were in the middle of a pandemic. All of my classes were online (which sucks), but I was happy. Nonetheless, I moved into my dorm, and my college life began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sat there for a minute to contemplate my life and how far I have come, but my imposter syndrome decided to make an appearance, so that killed my good mood. I have met some good people on campus but because of covid-19, meeting new people was risky and limited. Anyhow, my dorm was off-campus, and since I did not have a car going to get food to the dining hall was an adventure since I either had to walk or take the shuttle or ride with a friend. The food on campus was not too bad. I did get sick from it real quick, so most of the time, I was eating a protein shake or a rice cake with peanut butter. Something good from that was that I lost some weight, which is always good since I am overweight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first semester went well despite the pandemic, and it came to an end two weeks before Thanksgiving because that is when I moved back home. At the end of the semester, my grades were A’s in all of my six courses, which made me feel proud of myself. Here I am in week three of my second semester of college. My goal for this semester is to have all A’s again and finally learn to program. I have created this blog to hold myself accountable for documenting my journey to learning to program and in my college career.I will try my best to become a better writer because I want to tell my story and stories from people who are experiencing the same journey as me.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How I got a full ride to college]]></title><description><![CDATA[January 2020 I was scrolling through Twitter as usual, when out of nowhere, a tweet from thedream.us appeared on my timeline. I was…]]></description><link>https://fidel95.github.io/how-i-got-a-full-ride-to-college/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fidel95.github.io/how-i-got-a-full-ride-to-college/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;January 2020 I was scrolling through Twitter as usual, when out of nowhere, a tweet from thedream.us appeared on my timeline. I was intrigued because the headline said, “Scholarship for undocumented students”. I immediately clicked on it that link took me to their website, where I spent a few minutes reading the scholarship requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-story-short I started the application that day, but I thought it was too good to be true because, during that time, racism was fueled by president trump. I ended up leaving the application halfway done fast forward a few days later. I saw a tweet from thedream.us saying that it was the last day to submit the application, it was hours before the deadline, but I had to submit it because I used to work the second shift, and I knew I wouldn’t get home till midnight. So I decided to finish it and hope for the best; I wasn’t confident because I am not smart at all. I graduated high school with a 3.0 GPA and then went to community college to graduate with a 3.5 GPA. In my mind, I was like scholarships only go to recent high school graduates or really smart people (which I am neither of those two), plus I am an old soul (I was 24 at that time). Also, I wondered why a person or organization would offer an undocumented student a full ride to college?. Yeah, this is too good to be true, but I ended up submitting the application like what the hell do I got to lose? Nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, I clicked the submit button minutes before leaving to go work in a job where I was not happy at all, and most of the time, I felt depressed. Three months later, and quite honestly, I forced myself to forget about the application because I knew I wasn’t going to get the scholarship. So one day before the whole country shut down, I was on the treadmill at the gym when a notification from google Gmail popped out. This was the email I got:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com.au/&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot; style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; max-width: 630px; &quot;&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot; style=&quot;padding-bottom: 69.62025316455697%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&amp;apos;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABQAAAAOCAYAAAAvxDzwAAAACXBIWXMAABYlAAAWJQFJUiTwAAACXUlEQVQ4y31TS2sTURTOr3DrSpAKQre6Eh8ECinSarQW0YUigrosiBCRVJGUbhSUQqUUArrVjUhsWqs20TRBWhvzIi8mSfPOPDszST7nTHLHaFovHL5zTu75znfumdi63S7o6HobP38lEQptwr8eRDgURGAjgGBkB1uR79gKf8X29g7C4R/Y+OxHIPgNm+EINKOODuOxMYdv1uFdXkStwcPn+4Bb0+dx4eI1nBqbwu0bU3BdP45nT+7ijus5pifP4eyZ07jsvARRFPcn1PZkLC8uYH1tBbFkEu7Hcxg96YD9xAhGjh6BfeIqJp1OjI07cMU+imOHD2HCMQ5NVfYn1I0fFl7Mw7v0Cqurn+B954N7dhaeBzfx9NEMZlwe3H/ohv+tGytvPFiau4fXL+fR1eS/CfsR+rF5FC4H/ctHoMxB0buQJAWiIEIWBKPxnqFKt+726v4U2wbZLVYuC23tPbR0AkqjDqm8C7lWhVgsQNotoS2J6HS6/bqemKGRCVVNhaqq0Ehxv6Om61CMnKppPdR1q3mn07HUDRG2220Ui0UUCgWUSkUIfMsYUwDP82g0Gmg2m6jX66ZfLpfRarUwKMYa2dqyoSCVSiFpbJgh86PRKGKxGBKJBNLptIm5XA6C0ZARDikk+aRm0EgNKSGjYpqC7pEx/0BCert4PG4qIstkMqaKbDZrGamjHCHFsiwfTKgbj01vU6lUUK1WjU9FMgsIyegfoSiKmWN5iv9LSEvJ5/PgOM5cDiEpohwZ5VhMSPG/i7ExdloKXaRxWEGtVrPekxQxn9QSMoWDhL8B10n7z9C7kHIAAAAASUVORK5CYII=&amp;apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot; alt=&quot;scholarship&quot; title=&quot;scholarship&quot; src=&quot;/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/f058b/scholarship.png&quot; srcset=&quot;/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/c26ae/scholarship.png 158w,
/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/6bdcf/scholarship.png 315w,
/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/f058b/scholarship.png 630w,
/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/40601/scholarship.png 945w,
/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/78612/scholarship.png 1260w,
/static/64cbcaeb9ec9a05c8ce2168bbf2185fe/1d97b/scholarship.png 1993w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px&quot; style=&quot;width:100%;height:100%;margin:0;vertical-align:middle;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I tell you that, I immediately left the gym and headed home while one or two tears started dripping from my eyes. I cannot believe it for the first time something good happened to me in my life. I was awarded a full ride to college; never in my life would I see myself going to a four-year college mainly because I am an undocumented student, meaning that I cannot receive any financial aid. Colleges in America are too expensive. I know that first hand. After all, I struggled a lot when I went to community college because I worked a lot to make the monthly payments for the tuition barely. So, I don’t want to keep making this post longer than it should. I want to say that I am and will forever be grateful to &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedream.us&quot;&gt;thedream.us&lt;/a&gt; for giving me a chance to better my life and making me the first person in my family ever to attend college. I hope one day I can make a difference in someone’s life.I am a proud Dreamer and a proud college student from &lt;strong&gt;Delaware State University.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;I apologize for any grammatical mistakes. I am not a good writer. I promise that I will try to better myself.&lt;/h6&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hello Mundo]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have meant to create my first blog for the longest now, but I think today is the day that I can cross out that task from my todo-list…]]></description><link>https://fidel95.github.io/hello-mundo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://fidel95.github.io/hello-mundo/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 21:44:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I have meant to create my first blog for the longest now, but I think today is the day that I can cross out that task from my todo-list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog will hold me accountable for learning programming, which has been my goal for a while now. It will also help me document my life as a college student, and I can also upload school work here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is it for this first post. I do not know how many people will read this, but oh well, haber que pasa!.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>